-你在这干什么  -给你回信
- What are you doing here? - Answering your letter.
你说你很担心乌姆里奇
You said you were worried about Umbridge.
她在干什么
What's she doing?
教你们残害杂种生物吗
Training you to kill half-breeds?
小天狼星  她根本不让我们用魔法
Sirius  She's not letting us use magic at all.
她就是这样
Well, I'm not surprised.
最新情报
The latest intelligence is
福吉不希望你们做好战斗的准备
that Fudge doesn't want you trained in combat.
什么战斗
Combat?
他不会是觉得
What does he think,
我们在组织什么巫师军队吧
we're forming some sort of wizard army?
他就是这么想的
That's exactly what he thinks.
他觉得邓布利多要组织自己的
That Dumbledore is assembling
武装力量占领魔法部
his own forces to take on the Ministry.
他越来越偏执了
He's becoming more paranoid by the minute.
其他人不想让我告诉你这些  哈利
The others wouldn't want me telling you this, Harry